lostintechnology.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy|Lost in Technology

### Privacy

Lost In Technology respects your privacy.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Lost In Technology.

Credit card details

Lost In Technology will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Lost In Technology.

External Sites.

Lost In Technology is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

Cookies

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Lost In Technology to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Lost In Technology does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Lost In Technology and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Lost In Technology have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Here is a URL for more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:kyle.judkins@www.lostintechnology.com)
